Now let's say Audacity does another experiment,
现在假设优达学城要开展另一个实验
this time changing the order courses appear on their course list page.
他们准备更改各门课程在课程列表页面中的显示顺序
The metric they use is the overall click-through-rate to individual
他们要使用的指标
course pages.
是各课程页面的总体点击率
That is, the total number of times the user clicks on any course,
也就是说用户对任何课程的总点击量
divided by the number of page views.
除以页面查看次数
To give a consistent user experience of the course list,
为了就课程列表给用户提供一致的体验
while still including non-logged in traffic in the experiment,
同时记录实验中未登录用户产生的流量
Audacity chooses cookie as the unit-of-diversion.
优达学城选择将 cookie 用作分组单元
And they use their standard values of 0.05 and 0.2 for alpha and beta.
他们使用标准的 α 和 β 值 分别为 0.05 和 0.2
Their practical significance boundary, or dmin, is 0.01, and
他们的实际显著性界线 也就是 dmin 是 0.01
they empirically estimate that their standard error to be 0.0628 for
根据经验 他们估计在使用基于 cookie 的分组单元时
1,000 page views, sampled using cookie based diversion.
每千次页面查看的标准误差为 0.0628
The result is that Audacity would need at
结果显示优达学城需要每组至少产生
least 300,000 page views in each group in order to have enough power,
300,000 次页面查看才能获得见解
which would correspond to all of their traffic for a month.
这相当于他们一个月所获得的点击量
Audacity isn't willing to spend that long getting results on this
优达学城并不希望花那么长时间
one experiment,
来得出这一个实验的结果
especially if it means they can't run any other experiments in the meantime.
特别时 这种方法使得他们无法同时开展另一个实验
Which of the following strategies could Audacity try,
优达学城可能尝试以下哪种策略
in order to reduce the total number of page views needed to get a result?
来减少获得结果所需的总页面查看次数？
First, you already saw in lesson one, that they could increase the practical
首先 根据第一课的内容
significance boundary, that is, not try to detect a smaller change.
他们可能增加实际显著性界线 也就是不检测较小的更改
Or, alpha or beta, that is,
或者增加 α 或 β 也就是说
accept a higher probability of a false positive or a false negative.
接受较高的误报概率
So, this would work.
这个策略是可行的
But here are some other things they could consider changing.
但他们还可能考虑更改其他方面
First, would it help to change the unit of diversion to a page view rather
首先 将分组单元从 cookie 更改为页面查看
than a cookie?
是否会有帮助？
That is, if each page view was randomly assigned to the control or
也就是说 将每个页面查看随机分配至对照组或实验组
experiment group, even if two page views came from the same cookie,
即便某两个页面查看来自同一个 cookie
would this reduce the total number of page views needed?
这是否有助于减少所需的页面查看总量？
Second, would targeting the experiment to specific traffic help?
其次 将实验目标设定为特定点击量是否会有所帮助？
That is, suppose that Audacity has classes in many languages, and
也就是说 假设优达学城建立了多种语言的班级
this experiment only reorders the English classes.
而仅针对英语班级开展本次实验
So then, would it help to restrict this experiment to only the English traffic?
仅针对英语用户产生的点击量开展本次实验是否会有所帮助？
And finally, would it help to change the metric to a cookie-based
最后 将指标从点击率更改为
click-through-probability rather than a click-through rate?
基于 cookie 的点击概率是否会有所帮助？
Check any of these three changes that would reduce the total number of page
这三种更改中的哪些有助于减少所需的页面查看量？
views needed.
请将其勾选出来